-半夜 -不
- Night. - No.
-电话时分 我去接 -快接
- Middle of the phone. I got it. - Get it.
-我手臂睡麻了 我手臂睡麻了 -快接电话
- Oh! My arm's asleep! My arm's asleep! - Get the phone.
菲尔 接电话
Phil, get the phone.
那是我 你好
That's me. Hello! Hi.
是的 我是克莱尔
Yes, this is she.
是谁打来的
Who is it?
是吗 我的天
Okay. Oh, God.
快告诉我发生什么事了
Tell me what's happening here!
海莉被逮捕了
Haley has been arrested.
什么
What?
电话 电话 肯定是我妈
Phone! Phone. I bet that's mama.
我刚梦到天上下小鸡
I was just dreaming it was raining chickens!
米奇尔 接电话
Mitchell, answer the phone!
我不正接着嘛 不正接着嘛
Look what I am doing. Look what I am doing, huh?
-喂 -米奇尔
- Hello? - Hey, Mitchell.
抱歉吵醒你们 但海莉被逮捕了
I'm sorry to wake you up, but Haley got arrested.
天啊 海莉被逮捕了
Oh, God. Haley got arrested.
难怪我梦到小鸡了[女孩]
That explains the chickens.
没错 的确"很灵验"
It does. It adds up.
她为啥被抓了
What's she get arrested for?
她是因为在派对喝酒被抓的
Oh, she got caught drinking at some party.
你能和我们一起开车去学校吗
Look, could you drive up to the college with us?
-我们大概需要一个律师 -当然没问题
- I think we're gonna need a lawyer. - Yes, of course.
小卡和莉莉可以去你家陪着艾丽克斯和卢克
And Cam and Lily can come over and stay with Alex and Luke.
我誓将用生命守护他们
I'll guard them with my life.
我不愿意麻烦他
I hate to bother him.
不 别这么说 他很乐意帮忙
No, no, don't be silly. He's happy to do it.
好吧 我们一会儿就过来
Okay, we'll be over in a little bit.
行 我懂了
Oh, I get it.
当你告诉克莱尔我会去她家照看孩子时
When you told Claire I would come over and watch the kids,
她语气很抵触
She was resistant
因为她不信任我带孩子的能力
because she doesn't trust my parenting skills.
不 别说傻话了 她只是不愿意麻烦你
No. Don't be silly. She just didn't want to put you out.
她女儿都进局子里了
She's got a daughter behind bars
还敢指责我不会教育孩子
and she's got the nerve to say I'm a bad parent?
-你都不为我辩解 -因为她什么都没说
- You didn't defend me. - Because she didn't say anything.
你这么护着她干什么
Why are you protecting her?
怎么就没人护着我呢
Why is no one protecting me?
这套不行
No.
接电话 接电话
Ay! Answer! Answer!
你最好是有什么好事要说
This better be good.
海莉因为喝酒被逮捕了
Haley got arrested for drinking.
我们要去把她保释出来
We gotta go bail her out.
你和州北的法官还有联系吗
Do you still have a connection to that judge upstate?
-他已经死了 -谁死了
- He died. - Ay! Who died?
我的一个老友
An old friend of mine.
真令人遗憾 杰
Ay, Jay, I'm so sorry.
他五年前就死了
He died five years ago.
那他们大半夜把我们吵起来
Then why are they calling us in the middle of the night
是为了什么
to wake us up?!
没人死了 是海莉被抓了
Nobody died. Haley's in jail.
好 这还说得通
Okay. That makes more sense.
克莱尔要去保释她
Claire has to go bail her out.
好 电话给我
Okay. Give me that.
克莱尔 你听我说
Claire, listen to me--
带上大量的现金
Take a lot of cash.
然后在警察面前亮出绿油油的票子
And when you flash it to the police,
千万别张口提钱的事
Do not speak about it.
用眼神来交流 懂了吗
Let the eyes do all the talking, okay?
我听到有电话来 谁死了
I heard the phone. Who died?
杰的朋友
Jay's friend.
杰 太令人遗憾了
Oh, Jay, I'm so sorry.
够了 我听不下去了
Okay. I can't do this again.
早饭热腾腾
It's breakfast
早餐时间到
It's breakfast time
早早吃饭身体好
It's breaky breaky time
小卡舅夫 我就觉得听到你声音了
Uncle Cam. I thought I heard your voice.
你在我家干什么 我爸妈呢
What are you doing here? Where are my parents?
大学打了电话来 说你姐姐得了大奖
Well, the school called, and your sister won a big award.
编得不错 可这种谎言
Nice try. The only person
也只能骗骗海莉自己了
who would believe that Would be Haley.
她进监狱了
She's in jail.
监狱
Jail?
莉莉 我说过什么来着
Lily, what did I say?
说她进监狱是迟早的事
That it was only a matter of time.
不 我可没这么说
Okay, no. Didn't say that.
好吧 事情的真相是
Okay, so here's the truth.
你姐姐因为喝酒被抓了
Your sister was caught drinking.
但没什么大不了的
But it's no big deal.
你父母已经赶去了 正在处理这事
Your parents are there taking care of it right now.
所以
So...
太棒了
This is so awesome!
我希望她会在牢里开始健身
I hope she hits the weights
这样她出来时就化身肌肉女了
so she's totally ripped when she gets out.
好了 我们换个话题
Okay. Let's change the subject.
坐下来 吃点早餐
Have a seat. Have some breakfast.
看看盘子里有什么是你们最爱吃的
See if there's anything on that plate you like a lot.
这是培根吗
Is this bacon?
当然是了 小笨蛋
Of course it is, silly.
鄙人最近有点小沉迷于健康养生
Been on a little bit of a health kick lately,
所以我去上了素食烹饪课
so I took a vegan cooking class,
现在我最爱做的就是"素根"了
and my new thing is "Fakon."
跟真正的培根没有区别
It's like real bacon.
除了外观 口感和味道上的明显差异
Except for the look, the texture, and the taste.
超市里卖的可能如此
Maybe the store-bought kind.
但我的"素根"是自己做的 连"素根"都该算不上
But I make my own, so it's not even real fakon.
山寨素根 "山寨根"
It's faux-fakon. "Faux-kon."
反正是"根"难吃
It's faux-kon disgusting.
你根本就吃不出差别
You can't tell the difference.
猜猜哪一盘是真培根
And guess which one's the real one?
那一盘
That one.
还是那一盘
Still that one.
这是我吃过最香的培根了
This is the best bacon I've ever had.
太好了
Oh, well.
我恨不得马上告诉你米奇舅舅你喜欢这个
I can't wait to tell your uncle ,Mitchell that you love it.
为什么米奇舅舅在意这个
Why would uncle Mitch care?
亲爱的 因为
Because, my dear,
你现在吃的培根根本不是培根哦
that bacon you're eating isn't bacon at all,
不是哦
No, no, no.
完全由大豆制成
It's made entirely of soy.
卢克对大豆过敏
Luke's allergic to soy!
他的喉咙会噎住 不能呼吸
His throat closes! He can't breathe!
-你好 -没事了
- Hello? - Never mind!
好吧好吧
Okay, okay.
我们得马上把你送到那个 医院去
We have to, uh, get you to the, uh, hospital!
莉莉 来 宝贝
Lily! Come on, baby.
卢克 快把假培根放下
Okay, Luke! Put the fakon down!
我在用它挠我的喉咙
I'm using it to scratch my throat!
-好了好了 快走吧 快点 -走
- Okay. Okay. Let's go. Come on. - Go.
小卡 小 小卡
Cam? C-cam?
真奇怪
That was weird.
克莱尔 你能不能开快点
Hey, Claire, do you wanna pick it up a little bit?
你从什么时候起按限速开车了
Since when do you drive at speed limit?
我女儿因喝酒被捕了
My daughter has been arrested for drinking.
我希望她在监狱里痛定思痛
I would like her to sit in jail and think about that.
其实 我想停车
As a matter of fact, I might stop
上直销店买点东西
and do a little outlet shopping.
谁想要买一副去年款式的太阳镜
Who wants a pair of last year's sunglasses, huh?
亲爱的
Honey...
放松点
Try to relax.
我放松不下来 菲尔
I don't feel like relaxing, Phil!
她进大学才六个礼拜
She has been in college for six weeks.
没错 每个人刚去的时候都会有点疯狂
Yeah, and everyone goes a little crazy at first.
我记得大学头一年的一个晚上
I remember one night freshman year,
我们飞盘高尔夫球队的一些人
a bunch of us on the frisbee golf team
拿一箱芝马酒 不必多说
got a case of zima. Enough zaid.
说得够多了
More than enough.
说实话
I'm not gonna lie.
菲尔面对压力还那么淡定有时候让我很恼火
Sometimes it bothers me how calm Phil is under pressure.
感觉像是
It's like...
像是我反应过激了一样
like I'm the one who's overreacting.
很好 宣泄出来 这样
That's good. Let it out. It's g--
我要杀了你
I'm going to kill you.
杰 你今天有时间吗
Jay, do you have some time today?
我们得去选一辆婴儿车
We need to go and pick out a stroller.
你想买什么样的就买去吧
Just get whatever you want.
反正你也从来不会听我的意见
I mean, it's what you're gonna do anyway.
我想要的是一位
What I want is a husband
喜欢陪我逛街买婴儿车的丈夫
who likes to go shopping for a stroller with me.
如果你丈夫有挑选婴儿车的爱好
If you had a husband who liked picking out strollers,
你就不会怀上孩子了
you wouldn't be having a baby.
谁要陪我去
So who wants to come with me
今晚的演讲节
to the Spoken Word Festival this evening?
我只有两张票
I only have two tickets,
有人可能要失望了哦
so somebody's gonna be disappointed.
我想是你要失望了
I think it's gonna be you.
曼尼 我想跟你一起去 可是我好累啊
Ay, Manny, I would go with you, but I'm so tired.
你才刚刚起床 怎么会累
You just woke up. How are you tired?
因为我正在把食物加工成人
Maybe because I'm turning food into a human!
杰会带你去
Jay will take you.
抱歉 我也很想去
Sorry, I would love to go to the spoken word festival,
但我得去
but I'm already going to the
"不如炸掉我脑袋"狂欢节
I'd-rather- blow-my-brains-out jamboree.
难以置信
I can't believe this.
我居然生活在一片文化荒原
I'm living in a cultural wasteland.
配备温水泳池
With a heated pool.
曼尼 快点 上学快迟到了
Manny, vamos. You're gonna be late for school.
老天
Oh, jeez.
你好啊 迪迪
Hello, DeDe.
早上好 杰 合十致敬
Good morning, Jay. Namaste.
别这样
Let's not do this.
好吧 小傻瓜
Oh, fine, silly.
我在去奥哈伊的一家静修所的路上
I'm on my way to a retreat in Ojai,
既然我将路过市中心
and since I'm passing through town,
我想顺便拿那本相册
I thought I'd pick up that photo album.
现在可真不是时候
You know, it's really not a good time.
拜托
Oh, please.
好吧 我到街上等你
All right. I'll meet you on the street.
车窗打开 开慢点
Drive by slow with the window open.
我正担心迪迪发现歌洛莉亚怀孕了
I was dreading DeDe finding out that Gloria's pregnant.
迪迪很在乎的一件事就是
It's one thing DeDe's hung on to,
她是我孩子的母亲
that she's the mother of my kids.
考虑到她们以往的恩怨
And considering their history...
我想
I-I wanna...
-扭断你的脖子 -什么
- rip your head off! - What?
别这样 快停下
No! Please stop it! Whoa!
别 迪迪
Eh? No! DeDe!
我不希望还有第四轮较量
I wasn't exactly looking forward to round four,
特别是歌洛莉亚现在体积庞大 行动迟缓
especially now that Gloria's a bigger, slower target.
往常这时候我在吃早饭呢
I'd normally be having breakfast right now.
老爸好
Hi, dad.
克莱尔 有什么新进展吗
Hey, Claire. Any updates?
没有 不过我们快到了
Not yet, but we're almost there.
上次你来家里
Last time you were over at the house,
看了一本相册
you were looking at that photo album.
你把它放哪儿了
What'd you do with it?
老爸 那是我
Oh, dad, that was me.
我大概是把它放在吧台后面的架子上了
I think I put it on the shelf behind the bar.
你在那做什么
What are you doing there?
他们让我陪他们过来
They asked me to come along
以防他们需要位律师
in case they needed a lawyer.
他们不该请一位真律师吗
Shouldn't they have a real lawyer?
天呐 我们该不该呢
Oh, God. Should we?
我就是位真律师 各位
I am a real lawyer, people.
环境法也是法啊
Environmental law is a thing.
别对我的话那么挑刺
Don't get all sensitive on me.
我的意思是 别找个替大熊猫辩护的律师
I mean someone who doesn't defend pandas.
没错 老爸 那正是我的工作
Yeah, dad, 'cause that's what I do.
我在法庭上替大熊猫的权益辩护
I-I defend pandas in court.
真可爱
That's adorable.
你知道我是什么意思
You know what I'm talking about.
海莉需要懂刑法的人
Haley needs somebody who knows criminal law,
比如佩瑞·梅森 [美侦探小说虚构人物]
like Perry Mason.
所以我不是真正的律师 佩瑞·梅森倒是了
Okay, so I'm not a real lawyer, but Perry Mason is?
见鬼
Oh, hell.
你好 迪迪 你怎么样啊
Hello, DeDe. How're you doing?
还不错
Oh, mostly fine.
我安了一种叫做伸缩式子宫的东西
I have something called a telescoping uterus.
-说来话长 -上帝
- Long story. - Aw, jeez.
给我让开
Out of my way!
-让开 -我喘不上来气了
- Out of my way! - I can't breathe!
这孩子喘不上来气了
This boy can't breathe.
他有过敏反应
He's having a severe allergic reaction.
不是 是你压的
No. You're squeezing me.
他得吃药 他嗓子要堵上了
He needs medicine. His throat is closing up.
好 等等
Okay. Hold on.
有一名过敏反应病人
We have an allergic reaction.
是个小男孩 呼吸不畅
A young boy. Obstructed breathing.
怎么了
What happened?
有人给他吃了大豆做的培根
Well, somebody gave him some soy bacon...
做得太好了 他没看出来差别
That was so good, he couldn't tell the difference.
米奇尔 我现在说话不方便
Mitchell, I can't talk right now.
小卡 是克莱尔 我电话关机了
Cam, it's Claire. My phone died.
我就是想确认下孩子们已经顺利到学校了
I just wanted to make sure the kids got to school okay.
是的 他们当然去了 怎么会没有
Oh, yeah, of course they did. Why wouldn't they have?
-我听说有位男孩不能呼吸 -在这里
- I hear we got a boy who can't breathe? - Right here.
什么情况
What was that?
我正看一部生活台原创电影
Oh, I'm just watching an original Lifetime movie
叫做《不能呼吸的男孩》
called "The boy who can't breathe."
听着像艾丽克斯的声音
That sounded like Alex.
不是 是阿曼达·拜恩斯 我得挂了
Nope. Just Amanda Bynes. Okay, gotta go.
小卡 小卡
Cam. Cam?
奇了怪了
That's weird.
你能想象我们路过了多少家华夫饼店吗
Can you believe how many waffle places we passed?
我无法想象老爸有多么轻视我
I can't believe how much dad belittles me.
有多少来着 五家 六家
What were there? Five? Six?
我做过法律评论编辑
I edited the law review.
司法考试一次就过了
I passed the bar on my first try.
我还拎着公文包
I have a briefcase.
回去的路上我得数数
I'm counting them on the way back.
注意力集中
Can we focus?
你好 我们是为海莉·邓菲来的
Uh, hi. We're here for Haley Dunphy.
我是米奇尔·普里契特 邓菲小姐的律师
I'm Mitchell Pritchett. I'm Miss Dunphy's attorney.
她今天不需要律师
She won't be needing a lawyer today.
我觉得这该由我说了算
Oh, I think I'll be the judge of that.
我现在要和我的当事人谈谈 谢谢
I'd like to confer with my client now. Thank you.
你们只需要交上保释金就可以把她带走了
All you have to do is post bail, and she's all yours.
真的吗 那 那太好了
Really? Oh. That--that's fantastic.
长官 我今天真没想
Sir, I am in no mood
-袒护我的女儿 相信我 -好了
- to defend my daughter today, believe me. - Okay.
不过 你觉得因为校园里的孩子喝点儿酒
But do you think it is the best use of resources
就把他们押起来不是滥用公共资源吗
to lock up college kids who've had a few drinks?
女士 你的女儿被控拒捕
Ma'am, your daughter was charged with resisting arrest
并且袭警
and assaulting a police officer.
什么
What?
或许你该找个真正的律师
You probably should have called a real lawyer,
因为我吧 那个...
'Cause I don't... I'm not...
恐怕是有什么误会吧
Look, this has gotta be some kind of mistake.
我家女儿那么瘦小
Our daughter's tiny.
她怎么可能袭击别人呢
There's no way she assaulted anyone.
侮辱人还有点可能
Insulted, maybe.
那警察当时穿的是不是白袜子配黑皮鞋
Was--was the cop wearing white socks and dark shoes?
那种搭配会让她抓狂
'Cause that really sets her off.
或许你该看看这个
Maybe you should watch this.
停下
Stop!
把手放在我能看见的地方
Put your hands where I can see 'em!
这组镜头非常模糊
Okay. Now that's very blurry footage.
我们怎么确定那就是海莉
How can we be sure that that's Haley?
别动
Don't you move.
别伤害我 我只是一名学生
Don't hurt me! I'm just a student!
我叫海莉·邓菲
I'm Haley Dunphy!
真热啊
So hot.
这里真热
Hot in here.
还要多久
How long is this gonna take?
我应该上学去的 我已经错过了生物课了
I should be in school. I'm missing biology right now.
你可是在医院啊 只要走到走廊上
You're in a hospital. Just step out into the hallway.
听听医生护士们聊天
Listen to the nurses and doctors talk.
学到的科学知识和人性
You'll learn more about science and humanity here
比在课堂里待一学期学的都多
than you would in a classroom in an entire semester.
注意
Attention!
如果冰箱里有瓶写着"特丽莎"的酸奶
If there's a yogurt in the fridge that says "Theresa,"
那么只有特丽莎才能喝
then only Theresa gets to eat it!
生活如戏 好好学着
Drama. Soak it in.
-老天爷啊 -卢克
- Oh, good god. - Okay, Luke,
那衣服开口应该在背面
the opening is supposed to be in the back.
没门儿 我才不想别人看到我的屁股
No way. I don't want people to see my butt.
我还得打一针吗
Do I have to get another shot?
你又要哭了吗
Are you going to cry again?
-她有必要在这里吗 -得了 你知道吗
- Should she be here? - Okay. You know what?
不需要再打针了
Nobody's getting any more shots.
我们只要在这里等着消肿就行了
We just have to wait for the swelling to go down.
好吗 我得去看看一些文件
All right? I'm gonna go check on a little paperwork.
马上就回来
I'll be right back.
不过 如果不消肿的话
But if it doesn't go down,
就得卸掉你的腿
that leg might have to come off.
太好了 两条腿都卸了吧
Sweet. Take them both.
那我就能装上那种刀锋腿
Then I could get some of those blade legs
终于可以灌篮了
and finally be able to dunk.
感觉怎样 小子
How you feeling, champ?
我来看看是什么情况
What do we got here?
病人支气管发炎
The patient presents bronchial inflammation,
皮肤瘙痒 伴有轻度神经性水肿
Dermal pruritus, and minor angioedema.
谁能说出病因
Who can tell me the cause?
是大豆引起的过敏反应
It's an allergic reaction to soy.
很好
Very good.
其他人学着点 去下一病房
The rest of you have a lot to learn. Let's keep moving.
你守着卢克
Stay with Luke.
怎么这么久
What is taking so long?
以我的经验 这种事可能要等很久
Well, in my experience, these things can take time.
所以 坐好吧 估计要等上一阵了
So... settle in. This--this could be a while.
她出来了
There she is.
该死
Damn it.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank god.
-你还好吗 -我没事 妈妈
- You're okay? - Yeah, I'm fine, mom.
你当时脑子是进水了吗
Oh! What the hell were you thinking?
怎么回事
What happened?
没什么大不了的 好吗
It's not a big deal, okay?
我们在开派对 大家喝得正酣
There was a party, and people were drinking...
警察就过来了
so the police showed up,
所有人都往外跑 我也跟着跑
and everybody ran, so I did, too.
我顺着消防梯往下爬
And I started climbing down this fire escape...
然后我听到一个警察喊 把手举起来
And then I heard a cop yell to put your hands up,
我照做了 于是就掉...在他身上了
so I did and I fell... onto him.
你可能会没命的
You could have been killed.
海莉 你应该成熟一点了
Haley, you're supposed to be an adult.
怎么能做出这么幼稚的事来呢
How could you do something so childish...
-好了好了 -还这么愚蠢
- Okay, okay, okay, okay. - And so stupid?
冷静一下 我们都有点累有点暴躁
Let's calm down. We're all a little tired and cranky.
现在我们最好
Best thing we can do right now
出去买些华夫饼吃
is get out of here, go get some waffles--
菲尔 我不想买什么华夫饼 好吗
I don't want waffles, Phil, okay?
我很生气 我要处理这件事
I'm upset and I want to deal with this.
听着 我这里有个不好的消息
All right, I got some bad news here.
今天下午
Um, this afternoon,
海莉要接受纪律委员会的审讯
Haley has to appear before a disciplinary board,
而他们会决定是否要开除她的学籍
which will decide whether or not she gets kicked out of school.
什么
What?
慢着 等等 不对 我弄错了
Oh, wait. Wait, no. I got that wrong.
没有 我没弄错
Oh, no, I got it right!
好样的 了不起 加我一分
Yes! Score. One for me.
听起来虽然是那样
It's what it sounds like.
它真的会缩小
It literally telescopes.
是这样的
You see, what happens is...
迪迪 抱歉我不能和你聊了
DeDe, I hate to rush this,
我开会要迟到了
but I'm late for a meeting.
很高兴见到你 但我可以送你出去了吗
And it's been great seeing you, but can I walk you out?
好吧 当然
Okay. Sure.
杰 好奇怪
Ay, Jay, it's so weird.
我刚一进门
The moment I came through the door,
宝宝就开始疯狂踢我
the baby started kicking like crazy,
好像想从我肚子里爬出来似的
like it's trying to claw its way out of me.
老巫婆
Bruja!
天呐
Oh, my god.
她怎么会在这里
What is she doing here?
你们要有小宝宝了吗
You're going to have a baby?
难以置信
I don't believe it.
迪迪 别反应过度
Uh, DeDe, don't get all crazy about this.
这是怎么了
What's happening?
她脑子 坏掉了
Her brain. It snapped.
你这把年纪居然又喜当爹了
Oh! You're going to be a father again at your age.
而你还满心以为你可以
And here you were thinking
与你年轻漂亮的娇妻
you would just sail off into the sunset
安享晚年
with your beautiful young wife,
无忧无虑
not a care in the world.
这太美妙了
This is fantastic!
我觉得我的子宫就这么不治而愈了
I think my uterus just fixed itself.
什么也别问
Don't ask.
不是吧 怎么会有人过成这样
Oh no. Who lives like this?
我住宿舍的时候 那可是
When I had a dorm room, it was...
那是一尘不染的
oh--it was spotless.
大家同不同意女孩就是不如男孩爱干净
Can we just agree that girls are dirtier than boys?
-我们怎么办 -我觉得可以先从
- What should we do? - Well, I'd like to start
收拾这堆衣服开始 然后
by picking up some of these clothes. Then--
我是说听证会怎么办 威猛先生
I meant about the hearing, Felix.
我们有应对策略吗
Do we have a game plan?
我认为最好的策略是
I think the best thing we can do is
去表现出五好家庭的样子来
walk in there as a family
告诉他们无论如何我们都支持海莉
and let them know we support Haley no matter what.
照这样下去 我们下半辈子
At this rate, we are going to be supporting Haley
都得养着海莉了
for the rest of our lives.
好吧 我
Okay. Oh, I...
我屁股下面有半个桃子 不行
I just sat on half a peach, so I--no.
我忍不了了 我去外面等着
I can't do this. I'm--I'm waiting outside.
真恶心
Disgusting.
你穿的这是什么啊
What are you wearing?
怎么了 这有什么不妥的
What? What's wrong with it?
宝贝 你是要去跟纪律委员会
Honey, you are fighting for your future
为自己的未来作斗争
in front of a disciplinary committee,
不是去给特务机关提供娱乐服务的
not entertaining the Secret Service.
《律政俏佳人》里面的艾尔能打赢官司
In "Legally Blonde," Elle won her case
是因为她坚持自我 而且打扮俏丽
because she was true to herself and dressed cute.
海莉 这是现实生活
Haley, this is real life,
不是在演一部好电影
not an excellent movie.
宝贝 去找件别的衣服穿
Honey, just put on something else,
再把妆化淡一点
and take down the makeup.
你们干嘛表现得好像这都是我的错一样
Why are you guys acting like this is my fault?
每个人都喝酒了 也都逃跑了
Everybody was drinking, everybody ran.
我只是被逮住了而已
I just got caught.
我甚至算得上是受害者
If anything, I'm the victim here.
什么 别 别说了 海莉
What?! Just stop-- just stop talking, Haley.
你不是受害者 你犯了错
You're not the victim here. You're the one who screwed up!
你做了一个又一个错误的决定
You made one bad decision after another,
而现在你有可能会葬送你妈妈和我
and now you're about to blow everything
辛辛苦苦为你打造的一切
your mother and I worked so hard to give you.
最让人寒心的是 你看起来根本不在乎
And the worst thing is, you don't seem to care.
我们凌晨三点就起床
We all got up at 3:00 a.m. this morning
来保你出狱
to bail you out of jail!
一点东西都没吃
We haven't eaten a thing,
而你有些话到现在都还没说
and you know what I haven't heard from you yet?
"对不起 妈妈 我错了 爸爸
"I'm sorry, mom. I screwed up, dad.
请原谅我"
Please forgive me."
现在去找件正经的衣服穿上
Now put on some real clothes.
我们在听证会上见 不许迟到
We'll see you at the hearing. Do not be late!
走
Come on.
你们去哪儿
Where are you going?
去给那个男人买华夫饼
To get that man a waffle.
有了 有了 你感觉到它踢我了吗
There. There. Did you feel it kicking?
感觉到了 记忆犹新啊
Oh, yes! Oh, I remember those.
克莱尔一长腿就开始踢我
Yeah, Claire kicked me as soon as she grew legs,
长到4岁才不踢了
and she didn't stop until she was 4.
曼尼没这样
Not Manny.
他非常淡定
He was so calm,
我觉得他是在我肚子里看书呢
I think that he was reading in there.
太美好了
This is beautiful.
瞧你们两个 跟老朋友似的聊天
Look at you two, having a conversation like old friends.
她不掐我的时候很好相处
Well, it's easier to talk to her when she's not choking me.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
那是我的人生低谷
I went through a bad patch there
吃药吃的有点多
when I was trying to find the right balance with my Meds.
最近我发现我的猫弗朗西斯
I recently discovered my cat Frances
被埋在后院了
buried in the backyard.
我只祈祷它不是被我活埋的
I'm just praying that she died first.
或许哪天你能来当那条吃鞋狗的看护
Maybe you can dogsit for the shoe-eater one day.
那小东西长得真幽默
Oh, well, she is a... funny-looking thing.
别听她们的 你很漂亮
Don't listen to them. You're beautiful.
歌洛莉亚的大肚子倒是让迪迪
Turns out Gloria being pregnant
对她的敌意大减 反而关爱有加
somehow made DeDe think of her as less trophy, more human.
她对歌洛莉亚的憎恨
And all the animosity she had for Gloria
也全都烟消云散了
just wafted up in the air...
希望你雇了保姆
I hope you're hiring a nanny,
因为这家伙手都懒得抬一下
because this one won't lift a finger.
批评都落到我头上了
And landed right on top of me.
我记得他连一块尿布都没换过
I don't remember him changing a single diaper.
这话什么意思啊
What's that supposed to mean?
你连活埋了自己的猫都不记得
You can't even remember killing your cat.
我记得我没这么干
Oh, I don't think I did.
但是我很确定你从没换过尿布
But I'm sure that you never changed any diapers.
那只是因为你比我擅长换尿布嘛
It's just that you were better at it than I was.
这么说半夜喂奶 清理呕吐物
Oh, so I guess I was better at late-night feedings
我也比你擅长咯
and cleaning spit-up, too.
说到这个
You know what?
他也不愿意陪我挑手推车
He wouldn't help me pick up a stroller
毯子和婴儿摇椅
or a blanket or a bouncy chair.
那些东西我也是自己去买的
Oh, well, I had to get that stuff on my own.
他一点用都没有
He was just useless.
你太可怜了
You poor thing.
我算是知道你为啥变得这么疯了
Makes all sense now why you became so crazy.
是吧
Right?
听好了 杰·普里契特
Listen to me, Jay Pritchett.
你要是不肯把自己变废为宝
If you don't change your useless ways,
我也会发疯的
You're gonna make me crazy, too!
疯的像迪迪
Like DeDe!
歌洛莉亚 歌洛莉亚
Gloria. Gloria.
我可喜欢你来拜访了
I just love our little visits.
妈妈 我回来了
Mom, I'm home!
嗨 曼尼
Oh, hi, Manny.
迪迪 你好吗
DeDe. How are you?
很好
Good.
迪迪 是我呀
DeDe. It's me.
你到底怎么样啊
How are you really?
我的生活好多了
I'm on a better path.
生命是一次旅途
It's a journey.
谢谢你的关心 曼尼
Thank you for asking, Manny.
还有谢谢你的来信
And thank you for your letters.
那是门没落的艺术
It's a lost art.
没有人愿意用纸笔写信了
No one puts pen to paper anymore.
海莉·邓菲
Haley Dunphy?
没错 是我
Yes, that's me.
我是负责招生的院长米勒
I'm Dean Miller with admissions.
-这位是威廉姆斯教授 -您好
- This is Professor Williams. - Hi.
这位是我们的学生代表
And this is our student representative,
-艾顿·费德曼 -见到你很高兴
- Aidan Feldman. - Nice to meet you.
不是吧你
Seriously?
经济学课上我就坐你旁边
We sit next to each other in econ.
-哦 对呀 -少来
- Oh, right. - Don't.
对于你我都是一种侮辱
It insults both of us.
主要是对于我
Mostly me.
继续进行吧 艾顿
Move it along, Aidan.
这里是惩戒听证会 不是犹太交友网
This is a disciplinary hearing, not JDate.
你被控告公共场所酗酒
You are charged with public drunkenness,
拒捕 以及袭警
resisting arrest, and assaulting a police officer,
显然都违反了我们学校的行为准则
all of which obviously violate our school's code of conduct.
先生 容我代表我的委托人说两句
Sir, if I may speak on behalf of my client...
你是哪颗葱
Who are you?
在下米奇尔·普里契特
I'm Mitchell Pritchett,
邓菲小姐的律师
I'm Miss Dunphy's attorney.
我们要求学生为自己代言
We require students to speak for themselves.
不允许雇用律师 你都不应该来这儿
There are no attorneys allowed. You shouldn't even be here.
那我坐这儿保持沉默 侧耳聆听
What if I just sat in this chair and I was really super quiet
您意下如何
and I just listen?
准了
I'll allow it.
别闹了 艾顿
Knock it off, Aidan.
邓菲小姐 你有什么
Miss Dunphy, is there anything
要为自己辩护的吗
you would like to say in your defense?
事实上 我没什么可辩护的
Actually, I have no defense.
我是喝了酒 不到合法年龄
I was drinking. I am underage.
我逃避抓捕
I ran from the police.
虽说是意外 可我的确对那名警官造成了伤害
And even though it was an accident, I injured an officer.
我非常极其的抱歉
I am very, very sorry.
自从来到这里 我犯了很多错
I've made a lot of bad decisions since I've been here,
现在也该担起责任了
and it's time I take some responsibility.
比如有时候我在食堂里
Like sometimes in the dining hall,
他们给沙拉称重的时候我把称往下按了
I slip my pinky under the scale when they weigh my salad.
并且 我逃掉的晨课比上的还多
Also, I've missed more morning classes than I've been to.
我不知道电话约会的规则
I don't know what the policy is on dating T.A.S,
但我觉得我违反了
But I think I broke it.
-两次 -天呐
- Twice. - Oh, man.
要是绝对坦诚的话
Oh, and if we're gonna be completely honest,
我的大学申请书
on my application to get in here,
-我说了谎其实我是... -反对
- I lied about the fact that I was-- - Uh, objection!
-基于何种理由 -凭什么他就能说
- On what grounds? - Oh, he gets to say it?! He gets to--
邓菲小姐 邓菲小姐
Miss Dunphy, Miss Dunphy,
我们很欣赏你的坦率
We appreciate your... candor.
你还有什么要补充吗
Is there anything else you'd like to add?
加油 野猫
Go, wildcats?
我的天
Oh, boy.
野猫根本不是我们的吉祥物
That's not even our mascot.
这个是做什么的
What does this do?
不知道 不过多谢奥巴马 你买单
I don't know, but thanks Obama, you're paying for it.
你看起来好多了 感觉怎样
Hey. You're looking a lot better. How you feeling?
比那边的肾结石强多了
Better than kidney stones over there.
知道吗 现在你好转了
Yeah, you know what? Now that you're doing better,
我应该打电话给你妈 告诉她这件事
I think I should call your mom and tell her what happened.
我知道开头不是很顺利
You know, I know it was a bit of a rough ride in the beginning,
但重要的是 我处理好了
but the important thing is, is I handled it.
-大家都平安 -她这是怎么了
- And everybody's okay. - What happened to her?
-喂 -她在看剖腹产时晕过去了
- Hello? - She passed out watching a C-section.
小卡
Cam?
没事儿
Never mind!
你在找什么
What are you looking for?
没什么 我制造嗓音是因为我火大
Nothing! I am making a lot of noise because I'm angry!
歌洛莉亚 我会和你一起照顾宝宝的
Gloria, I'm gonna help you with the baby.
我现在不像生曼尼时那么年轻
I am not young like with Manny.
我已经很累了
I am tired already,
而且以后任务更艰巨
and it's gonna get harder from here!
我一个人没法搞定
I can't do this on my own,
我怀孕都是你的"杰做"
and you did this to me,
所以这次你要担起做父亲的责任
so you're going to be here this time!
那时候 我们的日子很拮据
Back then, we were living paycheck to paycheck.
我没有照顾孩子是因为我总在工作
the reason I wasn't around is I was working all the time.
相信我 不是只有迪迪一个人夜不能眠
Believe me,Dede wasn't the only one having sleepless nights.
现在不同了
But now it's different.
现在什么事我都可以帮你
Now I can help you with everything.
真的吗
Really?
从现在开始
Let's start right now.
-我喜欢这个 -哪个
- I like that one. - Which one?
银色的婴儿车
That silver stroller.
不 我们买那个绿色的
No, we're going to get the green one.
好的 接下来呢
Great. What's next?
我挑个你不喜欢的婴儿床怎么样
How about I pick out the wrong crib?
你还好吗 艾丽克斯
How you doing, Alex?
我很好 就是受到了严重打击
I'm fine, except for the crushing blow
知道自己永远不会做医生
of knowing I'll never be a doctor.
也不会生小孩
Or have a baby.
不知道海莉怎么样了
I wonder what's going on with Haley.
不知道
I don't know.
我今天一直不爽你妈怀疑我为人父的能力
I've been so petty about your mom judging my parenting,
我根本没想过她今天都经历了些什么
I haven't even thought about what she's going through today.
我感觉好糟糕 算了 我应该打给她
I feel awful. You know what? I should call her.
你说什么呢 我妈觉得你是个很棒的家长
What are you talking about? Mom thinks you're a great parent.
真的吗
She does?
是啊 她只是觉得你烤的东西难吃
Yeah, she just thinks you can't bake.
喂
Hello?
没事儿
Never mind.
造人是最简单的
Making a child is the easy part.
难的是后面接踵而来的事
The hard part is everything that comes after.
保护他们的安全
Keeping them safe...
你可以告诉你妈我的烤饼
Well, you can tell your mother that my scones
外面脆得恰到好处
are appropriately crunchy on the outside
里边绵密得让人爱不释口
while delightfully dense on the ins--
看见了 看见了
Saw that. Saw it.
为他们做出牺牲
Making sacrifices for them...
儿子
Hey, kid.
今晚我送你去参加那个诗歌朗诵什么的
I'll take you to that poetry reading thing tonight.
迪迪和我正在说这事儿
Actually, Dede and I were just talking.
她非常喜欢口语诗
She's a huge fan of spoken word...
我非常乐意送他去
And I would love to escort him.
-拜托了 -去吧
- Please. - Go.
支持他们 哪怕他们让你失望
And standing by them, even when they let you down.
真的对不起
I really am sorry.
好样的
We appreciate that.
你今天肯承担责任是好事
It's good that you stepped up today.
是啊 有时候一个新的开始也不错
Yeah. Sometimes it's healthy to get a fresh start.
难以置信 我该怎么办
I can't believe this. What am I gonna do?
他们说了你可以明年再申请入学
Well, they said you could reapply next year.
与此同时 你要找份工作
In the meantime, you're gonna get a job
上一些课
and you're gonna take some classes.
我会努力认真对待的
Well, I'm gonna buckle down and get a lot more serious.
-好样的 -对
- Good for you. - Yeah.
我的钥匙呢
Where are my keys?
在化妆台上
Oh, they're right there on the makeup table.
亲爱的
Oh, honey...
那是书桌
That's a desk.
我的天 你怎么回来了
Oh, my god. What are you doing here?
我被学校赶出来了
I got kicked out.
来吧 要笑尽管笑 有话尽管说
So go ahead, make your jokes. Get it out of your system.
不 那太糟糕了 真替你难过
No, that's horrible. I'm so sorry.
没事的 我肯定
It'll be fine. I'm sure of it.
谢谢
Thank you.
瞧你把我的房间弄的
Ew, what did you do to my room?!
这不全是你的房间 也是我的
Well, it's not exactly your room. It's--it's mine.
这个滚蛋 这个滚蛋 我讨厌那个
This goes. This goes. I hate that.
-这个好丑 -海莉 别这样
- This is ugly. - Haley, stop!
-妈 -妈
- Mom! - Mom!
这是什么 太阳系吗
What is this? A solar system?
那是分子
It's molecules.
就是傻蛋球
They're nerdy balls.
艾丽克斯 别跟她吵
Alex, don't fight with her.
她可能有刀
She might have a shiv.
我们没事吧
We cool?